

CONTACT

- SandstoneCandy@pm.me
- in https://linkedin.com/in/emperdeon
- nttps://github.com/EmperDeon
- ★ https://t.me/emperdeon

SKILLS

DevOps

Blockchain Nomad Docker Kubernetes GitHub CI/CD GitLab CI/CD TeamCity Grafana Prometheus Loki Hashicorp Vault



Linux Administration

Linux Ansible **AWS GCP** Bash/ZSH

Terraform



Developer

Git GitHub GitLab Rust Ruby \mathbb{C}^{++} JavaScript



LANGUAGES

- Russian Native
- **English B1**

ILYA BARYKIN SENIOR DEVOPS/LINUX ENGINEER

Industrious Senior DevOps Engineer offering 6-year background supporting developers in product management, setting up CI and CD pipelines, and developing internal tools. Well-rounded and conscientious professional committed to proactively managing change and quickly deploying critical applications.

EXPERIENCE

monitors.

Senior DevOps/Linux Engineer

Cryptology | 2023-04 - Present

- Participated in system development life cycle from requirements analysis through system implementation.
- Implemented deployment strategies using container orchestration tools such as AWS ECS and Nomad.
- Managed AWS assets and integrated multiple AWS resources into solutions appropriate for company projects.
- Maintained metrics visibility using Prometheus/Loki/Grafana to create useful dashboards and
- · Paid attention to detail while completing assignments.
- · Managed installation, upgrade and deployment of company projects.
- Proven ability to learn quickly and adapt to new situations.

Senior DevOps/Linux Engineer

WowSwap | 2021-08 - 2023-03

- · Worked with cross-functional design teams to create software solutions that improved overall functionality and performance.
- Implemented deployment strategies using container orchestration tools such as Docker and Kubernetes.
- Monitored automated build and continuous software. integration process to drive build/release failure resolution.
- · Wrote utilities to improve critical infrastructure and monitoring
- · Automated and implemented system backup and recovery procedures.
- Tuned systems to boost performance.
- · Investigated new and emerging software applications to select and implement administrative information systems.
- Implemented best practices to protect data and assets.
- · Demonstrated respect, friendliness and willingness to help wherever needed.

Middle/Senior DevOps/Linux Engineer

Edstein | 2019-07 - 2021-08

- Provided engineering support from code delivery of application.
- Built databases and table structures for web applications.
- Translated technical concepts and information into terms parties could easily comprehend.
- Tested and deployed scalable and highly available software products.

Backend Web Developer/Middle DevOps Engineer

Techinform | 2017-06 - 2019-06

- Created enhancements to resolve client problems and meet operational standards.
- · Built APIs and data clients to consume APIs.
- Troubleshot, tested and debugged software to clean up code and improve efficiency.
- · Managed efficient SQL queries and data transport.
- · Configured servers and managed provisioning.
- Authored code in Ruby and JavaScript within Rails framework.

EDUCATION

 College: Software Technician, Department of Programming

Ufa College of Statistics, Informatics And Compute - Russia | 2 013-09 - 2017-09

HOBBIES

- Exploring and trying new work-related software to solve issues and expand knowledge of available options.
- Developing small software and hardware projects.
- Traveling and meditation.
- Touch typing